All right. Good afternoon. My name is Zachary Short. I'm the primary developer of Furlough.
I'm going to demonstrate some of the functionality behind the NFC tags. These are three example NFC
tags that I purchased. You can buy them in a case of 50 for about $10. So they're about 25 to 50
cents per count. And all I'm going to do is run through the functionality that is required to
utilize the NFC tags. There is functionality that is not required to use the NFC tags,
but none of that is an issue today. So what I have here is the Furlough app. I can close out of it
fully and go back to it. So right now we just have the Furlough app and then an example app of the
functionality once it's been implemented. Right now I can open this because nothing's happened to it.
And if I go back to Furlough, you notice that I'm primarily being prompted to hold up an NFC tag to
the device. You can either scan the NFC tag from the front or from the back, but for the sake of
compliancy, I will show the NFC tag breaching the front of the device so that you can see it in view
the entire time. So right now, if I click "Hold a tag up", you can see that it is iOS's native NFC detection
sheet. And I will bring the tag in view up to the front of the device and it will detect it. And I
will give it a name like tag and I will pair it and it will suggest for me some places to put it such as a
bedroom or work, et cetera, et cetera. Now I can drop the anchor, which means that the NFC tag will block the
apps from opening and they can only be reopened by scanning the NFC tag. You do not need the NFC tag to
initially block the apps. So I will anchor it and I will decline these prompts, which are related to
sending the apps to my Mac. If I have one and now I will go back out of the app. You'll notice that
Instagram is now blocked. If I open it, it explains to me why I need to unanchor with my tag in
Furlough. So we'll do that now. We'll close the app, go back to Furlough and you'll notice here, I can
either click unanchor or I can click "Hold a tag up" for the sake of demonstration. I'll show you what
happens if you try to use a tag that has not been anchored before or paired. For example, this one,
bring it up. It says that it failed because that is not a known anchor. Now, if I go to unanchor the
original tag that we paired earlier, the apps unlock and I go back to my Instagram and I can open it.
This is the totality of the functionality involving NFC tags, which are commoditized and not proprietary
hardware with Furlough. Thank you.